Welcome to Burme Transcript App
This is a subtitle editing application
You can upload your own video files
And load SRT subtitle files easily
Click on any subtitle to edit in real-time
Use the time controls for precise adjustments
Customize font size and colors
Change background color and opacity
Adjust subtitle position on video
Set font weight and outline styles
Export your edited subtitles
Download as SRT, JSON or TXT format
Use keyboard shortcuts for quick control
Space = Play/Pause, Arrow keys = Seek
Use the sync slider to adjust timing
Split and merge subtitles as needed
Add new subtitles at any position
Search through your subtitle list
Dark and light theme support
Mobile friendly responsive design
Auto-save your work every 30 seconds
Style editor modal available
Click style button for more options
Choose from multiple font families
Adjust position to top center or bottom
Add outline for better visibility
Use precise time buttons for editing
Millisecond precision available
Sync all subtitles with offset slider
Enjoy editing your subtitles!